Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2013
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2013
Mus. Arc. 66
Haupt, Irene
3 DVDs (203 digital images in tiff format)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Contains 203 digital images of musicians who participated in the inaugural June in Buffalo Performance Institute and the June in Buffalo Festival 2013 at the University at Buffalo, including guest composers Raphaël Cendo, Brian Ferneyhough, Augusta Read Thomas, Charles Wuorinen, and Yehudi Wyner.
All files in the collection were renamed to reflect chronological sequence. Original filenames stated in the container list are transcribed as stated on the DVDs as received. Renamed files stored in the Institutional Repository.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Irene Haupt, 2013.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The entire collection of images from June in Buffalo 2013 is available in University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Irene Haupt, a graduate of the State University of New York at Buffalo, has been documenting the Buffalo arts scene through her photography since 1976. During that time she has worked for, or with, some of the most notable institutions in Buffalo, including the Irish Classical Theatre, Studio Arena Theater, the Kavinoky Theatre, the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, the Theatre of Youth, the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, and the State University of New York at Buffalo. In addition to her specialty of theater photography, Irene Haupt has also devoted much of her career to the photography of musicians and musical events. Most notable is her documentation of the contemporary music scene in Buffalo, including coverage of the University at Buffalo's June in Buffalo festival of new music, 1982-1987, and 2000 to the present. Over the course of those years, she has created a visual record that contains images of some of the most significant composers and performers of the last quarter century. The list of names is impressive: Aaron Copland, Morton Feldman, Leo Smit, Virgil Thomson, Steve Reich, Ralph Shapey, Henry Brant, Earle Brown, Ursula Oppens, Jan Williams, Lukas Foss, Philip Glass, Otto Luening, Conlon Nancarrow, Ernst Krenek, Larry Austin, Lejaren Hiller, Elliott Carter, Milton Babbitt, John Cage, Charles Wuorinen, Jacob Druckman, and Yvar Mikhashoff, among others.
The June in Buffalo festival of contemporary music was begun at the University at Buffalo in 1975 by composer Morton Feldman. He directed the festival 1975-1978 and in 1980. The festival was dormant from 1981 through 1985. David Felder revived the festival in 1986 and has been its director since that time.
Scope and Content Note
The collection of Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2013 contains 203 digital images of participants in the festival for 2013 as well as participants in the first June in Buffalo Performance Institute. The list of musicians includes guest composers Raphaël Cendo, Brian Ferneyhough, Augusta Read Thomas, Charles Wuorinen, and Yehudi Wyner. Performers include Irvine Arditti, Brad Lubman, Barry Crawford, Tom Kolor, Erich Huebner, Kenneth Radnofsky, Geoff Burleson, JoAnn Falletta, James Baker, and Jonathan Golove. Ensembles include the JACK Quartet, Ensemble Linea, Signal Ensemble, Talujon Percussion Ensemble, the Slee Sinfonietta, the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, and the Talea Ensemble.
Arrangement
One series arranged chronologically.
Container List
- Esin Gündüz, student composer and singer, at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-24, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: student composer ESIN Guenduez.tif (Image-file jib2013_001)
- Violinists Christopher Otto and Ari Streisfeld rehearse at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2349at M T Bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_002)
- Pianist Eric Huebner talks with violist John Pickford Richards at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2352Eric Huebner and Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_003)
- Violinists Christopher Otto and Ari Streisfeld talk with pianist Eric Huebner at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2358Jack Quartet with Eric Huebner at M T Bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_004)
- JACK Quartet rehearses at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2369Jack Quartet at M+T Bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_005)
- Student performers Matthew Geiger, Nicholas Emmanuel, T.J. Borden, Ross Aftel, Hangyu Bai, Michiko Saiki, Manuel Laufer, and Jade Conlee, read the program at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2373Performers of the Performing Institute.tif (Image-file jib2013_006)
- Student performers Matthew Geiger, Nicholas Emmanuel, T.J. Borden, Ross Aftel, Hangyu Bai, Michiko Saiki, and Jade Conlee, talk at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2376PI performers.tif (Image-file jib2013_007)
- Student performers Matthew Geiger, Nicholas Emmanuel, T.J. Borden, Ross Aftel, Hangyu Bai, Michiko Saiki, and Jade Conlee, at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2377Performers of the Performers Institute send.tif (Image-file jib2013_008)
- Pianist Eric Huebner and John Ganshaw, Vice President Manager Brand Integration at M & T Bank, at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2379Eric Huebner John Ganshaw M+T Bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_009)
- Violoncellist Jonathan Golove, pianist Eric Huebner, and John Ganshaw talk at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2383Jonathan Golove Eric Huebner John Ganshaw M+T bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_010)
- J. T. Rinker, Carolyn Tennant, and pianist Hangyu Bai at the reception for the JACK Quartet at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2384reception at M+T Bank for Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_011)
- Guests at the reception for the JACK Quartet at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2388reception for M+T Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_012)
- Violoncellist Jonathan Golove and other guests at the reception for the JACK Quartet at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2391reception at M+T Bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_013)
- Guests talking at the reception for the JACK Quartet at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2392reception at M+T for Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_014)
- Pianist Eric Huebner speaking at the JACK Quartet concert at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2396Eric Huebner at M+T Bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_015)
- Pianist Eric Huebner speaking at the JACK Quartet concert at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2397Eric Huebner at M T Bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_016)
- Pianist Eric Huebner speaking before a concert by the JACK Quartet at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2398Eric Huebner at M+T Bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_017)
- JACK Quartet at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2403 Jack Quartet at M T Bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_018)
- JACK Quartet at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2403Jack Quartet at M+T Bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_019)
- JACK Quartet performing at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2404Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_020)
- JACK Quartet performing at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2405Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_021)
- JACK Quartet performing at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2407Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_022)
- Sunset through the windows of the M & T Bank building in Buffalo at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2408at M+T Bank.tif (Image-file jib2013_023)
- Composer Colin Tucker at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Colin Tucker.tif (Image-file jib2013_024)
- Percussionist Ross Aftel and pianist Nicholas Emmanuel rehearse in room B-1 Baird at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2421rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2013_025)
- Percussionist Ross Aftel, pianist Nicholas Emmanuel, and violoncellist T.J. Borden rehearse in room B-1 Baird at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2426PI CLass with Telujon Stockhausen.tif (Image-file jib2013_026)
- Percussionist Ross Aftel and violoncellist T.J. Borden rehearse in room B-1 Baird at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2441Telujon Pi Class.tif (Image-file jib2013_027)
- Percussionist Matthew Geiger rehearses in room B-1 Baird at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2448Shapey Matthew Geiger.tif (Image-file jib2013_028)
- Pianist Eric Huebner and composer Eric Wubbels rehearse at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2504Eric Huebner Eric Wubbels.tif (Image-file jib2013_029)
- Title page of Elliott Carter's Sonata for violoncello and piano, 2013-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2506score.tif (Image-file jib2013_030)
- Violoncellist Jonathan Golove and pianist Eric Huebner rehearse at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2509Golove Huebner.tif (Image-file jib2013_031)
- Violoncellist Jonathan Golove performing Kottos by Iannis Xenakis at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2510Golove Xenakis.tif (Image-file jib2013_032)
- Violoncellist Jonathan Golove and pianist Eric Huebner performing Elliott Carter's Sonata for violoncello and piano at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2516Golove Huebner playing Carter.tif (Image-file jib2013_033)
- Percussionist Ross Aftel and violoncellist Jonathan Golove rehearsing Mauricio Kagel's Match in room B-1 Baird at a master class at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2517PI class with Golove playing Kagel.tif (Image-file jib2013_034)
- Percussionist Ross Aftel and violoncellist Jonathan Golove rehearsing Mauricio Kagel's Match in room B-1 Baird at a master class at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2526playing Kagel PI Class.tif (Image-file jib2013_035)
- Cover of the score for Milton Babbitt's Concerto piccolino for solo vibraphone, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2533 Babbit.tif (Image-file jib2013_036)
- Percussionist Matthew Geiger performs Milton Babbitt's Concerto piccolino at master class in room B-1 Baird at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2547performing Babbit for Yalujon PI Class.tif (Image-file jib2013_037)
- Percussionist Matthew Geiger listening to comments by percussionist Tom Kolor (far left) at a master class in room B-1 Baird at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2548 Talujon PI Class.tif (Image-file jib2013_038)
- Percussionist Ross Aftel and violoncellist T.J. Borden perform Chinary Ung's Spirals at a master class in room B-1 Baird at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2552performing Stockhausen for PI Class.tif (Image-file jib2013_039)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Matt Ward, David Cossin, Michael Lipsey, and Tom Kolor speaking at a master class in room B-1 Baird at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2558 Talujon PI Class.tif (Image-file jib2013_040)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Matt Ward, David Cossin, Michael Lipsey, and Tom Kolor speaking at a master class in room B-1 Baird at the 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute, with Jonathan Golove and Matthew Geiger in background, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2561Talujon Pi Class.tif (Image-file jib2013_041)
- Jack Quartet with pianist Eric Huebner rehearsing David Felder's Stuck Stucke at June in Buffalo 2013, with David Felder in the audience, 2013-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2574Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_042)
- Jack Quartet with pianist Eric Huebner rehearsing David Felder's Stuck Stucke at June in Buffalo 2013, with David Felder in the audience, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2576Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_043)
- Jack Quartet with pianist Eric Huebner rehearsing David Felder's Stuck Stucke at June in Buffalo 2013, with David Felder in the audience, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2577Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_044)
- Charles Wuorinen watches Christopher Otto rehearse at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2578 Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_045)
- Jack Quartet with Charles Wuorinen and Eric Huebner at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2583Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_046)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members David Cossin, Michael Lipsey, Tom Kolor, Matthew Ward, and Ian Antonio at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2593Talujon.tif (Image-file jib2013_047)
- Violoncellist Jonathan Golove speaking at a 2013 June in Buffalo Performance Institute class in room B-1 Baird, with violoncellist T. J. Borden and percussionist Ross Aftel in the background, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2606Golove Pi Class.tif (Image-file jib2013_048)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2620Talujon.tif (Image-file jib2013_049)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2623Talojon.tif (Image-file jib2013_050)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2624 Talujon.tif (Image-file jib2013_051)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2625 Talujon Percussion Ensemble.tif (Image-file jib2013_052)
- Tom Kolor, David Cossin, and Michael Lipsey, members of the Talujon Percussion Ensemble, performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Talujon Percussion Ensemble (2).tif (Image-file jib2013_053)
- Tom Kolor, David Cossin, and Michael Lipsey, members of the Talujon Percussion Ensemble, performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Talujon Percussion Ensemble.tif (Image-file jib2013_054)
- Tom Kolor and David Cossin, members of the Talujon Percussion Ensemble, performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2634 Talujon.tif (Image-file jib2013_055)
- Tom Kolor, David Cossin, and Michael Lipsey, members of the Talujon Percussion Ensemble, performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2645 Talujon.tif (Image-file jib2013_056)
- David Cossin and Michael Lipsey, members of the Talujon Percussion Ensemble, performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2651Talujon.tif (Image-file jib2013_057)
- Tom Kolor, David Cossin, and Michael Lipsey, members of the Talujon Percussion Ensemble, taking a bow at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2657Talujon.tif (Image-file jib2013_058)
- Eric Huebner and the JACK Quartet rehearse with Charles Wuorinen in the audience at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: tJack Quartet in rehearsal with Charles Wuorinen.tif (Image-file jib2013_059)
- Student composers Steven Weimer, Eric Stewart, Francis Heery, James Young, Brien Henderson, Clinton Haycraft, Nicholas DeMaison, Tomas Gueglio, Megan Grace Beugger and Matthew Sargent at June in Buffalo 2013 Composers of the works performed at the 2013 June in Buffalo festival, at the Performance Institute, 2013-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2684 Composer Perfroming Institute send.jpg (Image-file jib2013_060)
- Yehudi Wyner, composer and pianist, at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2687Yehudi Wyner.tif (Image-file jib2013_061)
- Raphael Cendo, composer, lecturing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2729Raphael Ceno.tif (Image-file jib2013_062)
- Raphael Cendo, composer, lecturing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2733Raphael Cendo lecture.tif (Image-file jib2013_063)
- Daniel Bassin and trumpeter Tim Leopold at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2739Daniel Bassin Tim.tif (Image-file jib2013_064)
- Charles Wuorinen speaking with singers Laura Mercado Wright and Sharon Harms at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2743Wuorinen with singers.tif (Image-file jib2013_065)
- Charles Wuorinen rehearses It Happens Like This with the Slee Sinfonietta and tenor Steven Brennfleck at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2754Rehearsal It Happens Like This by Charles Wuorine.tif (Image-file jib2013_066)
- Trombonist and trumpeter Tim Leopold of the Slee Sinfonietta rehearse Charles Wuorinen's It Happens Like This at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2755rehearsal for Wuorinen.tif (Image-file jib2013_067)
- Charles Wuorinen conducting rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2756Charles Wuorinen conducting.tif (Image-file jib2013_068)
- Charles Wuorinen conducting rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2757Charles Wuorinen-.tif (Image-file jib2013_069)
- Charles Wuorinen conducting rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2759 Charles Wuorinen.tif (Image-file jib2013_070)
- Charles Wuorinen conducting rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2765Charles Wuorinen---.tif (Image-file jib2013_071)
- Charles Wuorinen conducting rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2769Charles Wuorinen--.tif (Image-file jib2013_072)
- Charles Wuorinen at rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2771Charles Wuorinen-----.tif (Image-file jib2013_073)
- Percussionist Ian Antonio and composer James Young looking at a score together at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2773 rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2013_074)
- Ensemble Linea members Maiko Matsuoka and Jessica Rona rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2776 rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2013_075)
- Brian Ferneyhough at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2780Brian Ferneyhough==.tif (Image-file jib2013_076)
- Brad Lubman conducting SIGNAL Ensemble in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2787SIGNAL rehearsing.tif (Image-file jib2013_077)
- Eric Huebner, Matthew Ward, and Tom Kolor rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2806rehearsing.tif (Image-file jib2013_078)
- Tom Kolor rehearsing on interior of piano at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2813rehearsing.tif (Image-file jib2013_079)
- Tom Kolor and Nicholas DeMaison rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2821rehearsing with Tom Kolor.tif (Image-file jib2013_080)
- Student performers T.J. Borden, Nicholas Emmanuel, and Ross Aftel rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2822 rehearsing.tif (Image-file jib2013_081)
- Nicholas DeMaison and Tom Kolor preparing piano, with Daniel Bassin and Eric Huebner in background at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2824 rehearsing.tif (Image-file jib2013_082)
- David Cossin looking at score with composer Ben Phelps at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2826rehearsing.tif (Image-file jib2013_083)